Palakkad, Kerala | Email: anirudhwarrier@qmail.com | Mobile: (+91) 88-91-550070

GitHub: https://github.com/anirudhwarrier | Web: https://anirudhwarrier.com | LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/anirudhwarrier

Summary

Highly skilled Software Quality Assurance and Test Automation specialist, with more than 6 years of experience in the field. My contributions towards processes and frameworks, as well as my leadership skills, have been well-recognized, resulting in a proven track record of leading teams towards success. I am highly self-driven and motivated, possessing in-depth work experience in test automation and performance engineering. My passion for continuous learning and improvement, combined with my desire to contribute to making the world a better place, drives me to seek out new opportunities and challenges in my field.

Skills

Blockchain Testing • Performance Testing • Performance Profiling/Engineering • Gatling • Apache JMeter • AWS • Kubernetes • Test Automation • Go Lang • Docker • Java • DataDog • Kibana • JIRA • Git • GitHub • Jenkins • DevOps • White-Box Testing • Linux • Performance Tuning - PostgreSQL • Distributed Networks

Professional Experience

Chainlink Labs

Quality Assurance Engineer

Remote - Kerala, India

January 2022 - Present (1y5m)

Enhance security and reliability of the Chainlink node. Effectively implemented and executed robust quality assurance practices, thereby increasing the efficiency of the release process. Worked on testing of integrations to new blockchains. Effectively streamlined the testing lifecycle of Chainlink Automation by implementing rigorous testing methodologies. Collaborate with global cross-functional teams to gather requirements and ensure effective test coverage, resulting in seamless integration of quality assurance processes within the organization. Actively pursued opportunities to optimize and automate testing procedures, contributing to the improvement of

the test framework. Work hand in hand with a high velocity team and ensure every feature released is bug free. Engaged with external operations to provide node operators with high quality setup instructions. Engaged with the internal infrastructure team for smooth

release of new features.

QBurst Technologies

Thrissur, Kerala, India

Senior Quality Assurance Engineer

October 2018 - December 2021 (2y10m)

Lead for the Performance Engineering team, mentored and grew the team from 2 to 6 members. Understanding NFRs and defining performance test strategy. Defining performance targets and budgets. Preparing Performance Test Plan. Setting up Test Infrastructure. Evaluating load testing tools. Automation of tasks, developing scripts and tools. Performance Test Framework design for automation. Performance monitoring dashboard setup (Grafana & AWS CloudWatch)

CSS Corp

Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India

Engineer - Performance Testing & Engineering

August 2016 - October 2018 (2y2m)

Part of a dedicated performance testing and engineering team. Writing Performance test cases and scenarios. Performance test scripting (LoadRunner, JMeter). Performance monitoring using APMs (NewRelic, DynaTrace). Front end optimization (WebPageTest, In-house tool) analysis. Development of in house tools and frameworks.

Education

University of Calicut, Aug 2012 - May 2016 | B.Tech in Computer Science & Engineering | GPA 6.79/10

Certifications

IIT Madras & Great Learning, Dec. 2020 - Oct. 2021 | Advanced Certification in Software Engineering - Cloud, IoT & Blockchain